<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="liveupdate_langauge">english</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_language_chinese">chinese</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses_content">" "<b>Bouncy Castle</b>"

 Copyright © 2000 - 2013 The Legion Of The Bouncy Castle (http://www.bouncycastle.org)

 Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the Software), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: 

 The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

 THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.


 "<b>Protobuf</b>"

 Copyright 2008, Google Inc.
 All rights reserved.

 Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

   Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
   Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
   Neither the name of Google Inc. nor the names of its ontributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

 THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS AS IS AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

   Code generated by the Protocol Buffer compiler is owned by the owner of the input file used when generating it. This code is not standalone and requires a support library to be linked with it. This support library is itself covered by the above license.


 "<b>Google Gson</b>"

 Apache License
 Version 2.0, January 2004
 http://www.apache.org/licenses/

 TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

 1. Definitions.

   License shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

   Licensor shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.

   Legal Entity shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, control means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

   You (or Your) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License.

   Source form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files.

   Object form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.

   Work shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below).

   Derivative Works shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

   Contribution shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, submitted means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as Not a Contribution.

   Contributor shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.

 2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

 3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed.

 4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions:

   (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and

   (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and

   (c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and

   (d) If the Work includes a NOTICE text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.

 You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License.

 5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

 6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

 7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an AS IS BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

 8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

 9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

 END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

 APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.

   To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets [] replaced with your own identifying information. (Don`t include the brackets!) The text should be enclosed in the appropriate comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a file or class name and description of purpose be included on the same printed page as the copyright notice for easier identification within third-party archives.

 Copyright 2008-2011 Google Inc.

 Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the License); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an AS IS BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.


 "<b>Jsoup</b>"

 The MIT License
 Copyright © 2009 - 2013 Jonathan Hedley (jonathan@hedley.net)

 Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the Software), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

 The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

 THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
 "</string>
    <string name="app_name">Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="cloud_connect_permission">Norton Cloud Connect</string>
    <string name="app_title"><b>Norton Mobile Security</b></string>
    <string name="home_page"><b>Norton™</b> Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="product_name">Norton Mobile</string>
    <string name="anti_theft">Anti-Theft</string>
    <string name="anti_malware">Anti-Malware</string>
    <string name="call_blocking">Call Blocking</string>
    <string name="subscription">Subscription %1$d Days Left</string>
    <string name="subscription_active">Subscription Active</string>
    <string name="subscription_sync_license">Synchronize License</string>
    <string name="new_badge">NEW</string>
    <string name="renew">Renew</string>
    <string name="network_settings">Go to Settings</string>
    <string name="network_requirement_tips">An active Internet connection is required. Check your network settings and try again.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_available">A new version is available.</string>
    <string name="liveudpate_hint">A new version of Norton Mobile Security has been released. Click OK to download and install it.</string>
    <string name="billingcycle_monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="menu_setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_activitylog">Activity Log</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_other_app">Other Norton Apps</string>
    <string name="feature_overview"><b>Norton™</b> Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="feature_scan">Anti-Malware</string>
    <string name="feature_anti_theft">Anti-Theft</string>
    <string name="feature_app_advisor">App Advisor</string>
    <string name="feature_backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="feature_call_block">Call Blocking</string>
    <string name="feature_web_protect">Web Protection</string>
    <string name="feature_other_norton">Norton Apps</string>
    <string name="settings_set_by_administrator">Set by administrator</string>
    <string name="remove_malware">Remove Malware</string>
    <string name="malware_scan_alarm">MalwareScanAlarm</string>
    <string name="lu_scd_def_prefix">Submission control data application definitions</string>
    <string name="scan_sdcard">Scan SD Card: </string>
    <string name="scan_sdcard_hint">May affect scan time and device performance.</string>
    <string name="scan_btn">Scan</string>
    <string name="scan_period_label">Scheduled Scan: </string>
    <string name="malware_scan_uninstall_dlg_title">Norton Security has discovered a malicious file and will help you remove it.</string>
    <string name="start_malware_scan">Anti-Malware</string>
    <string name="malware_scan_uninstall_confirm">Remove</string>
    <string name="malware_scan_uninstall_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="sche_scan_delay_hint">Scheduled scan is postponed to save power.</string>
    <string name="norton_installer">Norton installer</string>
    <string name="scanning_title">Scanning</string>
    <string name="attention">Malware found</string>
    <string name="single_need_attention">Issue Found</string>
    <string name="multiple_need_attention">Issues Found</string>
    <string name="sdcard_enable_when_running_hint">Your settings changes will take effect on your next scan.</string>
    <string name="log_com_malwarescan">Malware Scanner</string>
    <string name="log_malware_real_scan_found">Found malicious app: {0}.</string>
    <string name="log_malware_real_scan_unknown">Unnamed</string>
    <string name="log_malware_scan_run">Malware scan ran.</string>
    <string name="log_scan_schedule_cancel">Another scan is running, cancel scheduled scan.</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_content_title">Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_text_license_remaining">Subscription days remaining: %1$d</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_text_license_expired">Your product has expired.</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_text_license_manual_sync">Please manually synchronize license.</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_text_license_canceled">Your license has been canceled.</string>
    <string name="notification_preinstall_activation">Activate now to protect your device.</string>
    <string name="ongoing_notification">Ongoing Notifications</string>
    <string name="ongoing_notification_hint">Display security status</string>
    <string name="convert_to_freemium">Converted to Lite Version</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_text_license_premium_remaining">Convert to Lite version after %1$d</string>
    <string name="lite">Lite</string>
    <string name="protection_summary">Protection Summary</string>
    <string name="protection_summary_available">Protection Summary</string>
    <string name="protection_summary_notify_content">View your activities.</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="limited">Limited</string>
    <string name="protect_summary_recomm">Available with Full version.</string>
    <string name="remote_locate_times">Remote locates: %d</string>
    <string name="remote_scream_times">Remote screams: %d</string>
    <string name="remote_lock_times">Remote locks: %d</string>
    <string name="remote_wipe_times">Remote wipes: %d</string>
    <string name="freemium_anti_theft_recomm">"Remote Lock only
Full version adds remote locate, wipe and scream."</string>
    <string name="freemium_anti_theft_recomm_fullversion">"Remote Lock, Locate, Wipe and Scream.
Available with Full version."</string>
    <string name="total_scan">Total files scanned: %d</string>
    <string name="malware_found">Malware found: %d</string>
    <string name="last_scan">Last scanned: </string>
    <string name="calls_block">Calls blocked: %d</string>
    <string name="sms_block">Messages blocked: %d</string>
    <string name="not_available">Not Available</string>
    <string name="web_page_scan">Web pages scanned: %d</string>
    <string name="web_site_block">Websites blocked: %d</string>
    <string name="web_protection_recomm">"Protects you from fraudulent websites.
Available with Full version."</string>
    <string name="backup_last_backup_time">Last backup: %s</string>
    <string name="backup_summary_title">Backup</string>
    <string name="backup_recomm">"You can backup and restore your contacts.
Available with Full version."</string>
    <string name="liveupdate">LiveUpdate</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_upgrade_notification_message">New version available for installation.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_upgrade_guide1">A new version of Norton Mobile Security has been downloaded, but cannot be installed because your device blocks applications from unknown sources. To install the new version, change the setting to allow these applications. After installation, be sure to block unknown sources again.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_upgrade_guide3">A new version of Norton Mobile Security providing enhanced protection for your device has been downloaded. Do you want to install it?</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_upgrade_go_to_settings">Go To Settings</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_complete">LiveUpdate finished: %1$d update(s) completed.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_finished">LiveUpdate finished.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_up_to_date">LiveUpdate finished: All components are up to date.</string>
    <string name="liveudpate_log_error">Could not download an update</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_low_battery">LiveUpdate canceled: Low battery.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_connect_failure">LiveUpdate canceled: Could not connect to the LiveUpdate server.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_roaming_disabled">LiveUpdate off because network is roaming.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_network_issue">LiveUpdate failed: network timeout or no network available.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_install_success">%1$s updated to version %2$s.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_already_latest_version">No update needed: %1$s is already the latest version.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_apk_downloaded">Update version %1$s downloaded.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_apk_upgrade">Update installed.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_exception">Could not install an update for downloading error.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_failed_mkdir">Not enough space for update.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_log_error">LiveUpdate error.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_downloading">Downloading …</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_no_network">No network available.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_scd_component_description">Submission control data</string>
    <string name="eula_title_string">Welcome to Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="eula_link_string">Norton License Agreement and Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="eula_agree_btn_string">Agree &amp; Launch</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_string">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="allow_collector_check_box_string">Enable Norton Community Watch</string>
    <string name="enable_ncw_hint">Fight against digital cybercrime, automatically forward security information to Symantec</string>
    <string name="allow_collector_check_box_string_1">I want to join Norton Community Watch in the fight against cybercrime by letting my device automatically forward security information to Symantec (Recommended).</string>
    <string name="found_other_norton_warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="remove_other_norton">You have another version of Norton Mobile Security that you must uninstall to avoid system conflicts with this version.</string>
    <string name="remove_myself">A version of Norton Mobile Security is already installed on your device. Please click Uninstall to remove this version.</string>
    <string name="uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="web_protection">Web Protection</string>
    <string name="btn_setup_webprotection_accessibility_service">Set Up</string>
    <string name="enable_web_protection">Web Protection</string>
    <string name="web_protection_blocked_pages_count_title">Blocked Pages:</string>
    <string name="web_protection_guide">"(Web Protection needs a stable network connection to work effectively)

You can continue to a blocked site if you think that the site is safe. The site will be unblocked for 30 minutes.

"</string>
    <string name="notify_text_webprotection_added_browsers">To support Opera and Firefox, tap Set Up, then find App Advisor by Norton, and turn it ON.</string>
    <string name="web_protection_guide_default_browsers">Turn on Web Protection to block fraudulent sites on Android browsers, Chrome and Chrome Beta.</string>
    <string name="web_protection_guide_added_browsers">Turn on Web Protection to block fraudulent sites on Android browsers, Chrome, Chrome Beta, Opera and Firefox.</string>
    <string name="safeweb_redirect_html" formatted="false">"&lt;html> &lt;head> &lt;meta http-equiv=\"Content-Type\" content=\"text/html charset=UTF-8\"> &lt;meta name=\"viewport\" content=\"width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0\"> &lt;meta http-equiv=\"Expires\" CONTENT=\"0\"> &lt;meta http-equiv=\"Cache-Control\" CONTENT=\"no-cache\"> &lt;meta http-equiv=\"Cache-Control\" CONTENT=\"no-store\"> &lt;script type='text/javascript'> function redirect(){window.location.href=\"%block_href%\"} &lt;/script> &lt;title>Redirect&lt;/title> &lt;style type=\"text/css\"> p,h1 {margin-bottom: 16pxpadding:} h1 {color: #111111font-size: 20pt} p {font-size: 16pt} &lt;/style> &lt;/head> &lt;body onload='redirect()'> &lt;noscript> &lt;h1>%prompt_title%&lt;/h1> &lt;p>%prompt_content%&lt;/p> &lt;/noscript> &lt;/body> &lt;/html>"</string>
    <string name="wrs_phish">PHISH</string>
    <string name="wrs_brexp">BREXP</string>
    <string name="wrs_virus">VIRUS</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="login_required_title">Sign-in required</string>
    <string name="login_required">Please sign in.</string>
    <string name="error_no_connection">Network connection error. Please check your data connection settings.</string>
    <string name="authentication_failed">Authentication failed. Please make sure your device time is correct.</string>
    <string name="contact_support1">Please contact</string>
    <string name="contact_support2">for help.</string>
    <string name="device_name">Device Name:</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="PleaseWait">Please wait…</string>
    <string name="capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="legal_text_on_lockscreen">This device is equipped with Norton Mobile Security, please return it to its legitimate owner. If you continue to use this device, you consent that it will collect your location and/or images of you and transmit it to Symantec Corp. in the US.</string>
    <string name="btn_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="btn_no">No</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="unbind_device_msg">Device has been removed.</string>
    <string name="error_occur">An unknown error has occurred. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_connection_timeout">Connection timed out.</string>
    <string name="error_connection_unknown_host">Network connection error. Please check your data connection settings.</string>
    <string name="error_connection_exception">Network connection error. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_ssl_cert_path_validation">Server certificate time mismatch: please make sure your device time is correct.</string>
    <string name="error_ssl_cert_not_found">Certificate cannot be validated on your device. Please make sure your device time is correct.</string>
    <string name="title_at_no_connect">Cannot connect to server</string>
    <string name="title_at_on">Anti-Theft is on</string>
    <string name="title_at_loc_off">"Location service is off
"<u>Tap here to fix</u></string>
    <string name="nat_web_hint">"For the Web commands, go to:
%s"</string>
    <string name="device_admin">Security Lock</string>
    <string name="device_admin_desc">Adds a level of protection for your device</string>
    <string name="device_admin_tips">Prevents uninstall of Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="security_wipe">Security Wipe</string>
    <string name="security_wipe_desc">Wipes your device after 10 failed unlock attempts</string>
    <string name="sim_lock">SIM Card Lock</string>
    <string name="sim_lock_desc">Locks the device if SIM card is removed or changed</string>
    <string name="device_admin_info">Activate Norton Mobile Security as your Device Administrator and make it even harder for malicious apps to bypass your lock screen or uninstall the security on your device.</string>
    <string name="at_full_version">Using SMS or on the Web, you can:</string>
    <string name="at_admin_version">Your device administrator can:</string>
    <string name="at_no_sms_version">On the Web, you can:</string>
    <string name="at_admin_no_sms_version">Your device administrator can:</string>
    <string name="at_lite_version">Using SMS, you can:</string>
    <string name="at_upgrade_to_version">Upgrade to Premium to add:</string>
    <string name="at_lock_devcie">Lock your device</string>
    <string name="at_remote_scream">Remote scream</string>
    <string name="at_locate_device">Locate your device</string>
    <string name="at_sneak_peek">Sneak peek (Web only)</string>
    <string name="at_wipe_device">Wipe your device</string>
    <string name="at_start_trial_button">Start FREE Premium Trial</string>
    <string name="unlock_by_passcode_title">Device Lock</string>
    <string name="unlock_help_title">Unlock Help</string>
    <string name="unlock_by_passcode_message_sim_card">Device locked because you have recently changed your SIM card.</string>
    <string name="locked_by_sms_command">Device is locked by SMS command.</string>
    <string name="unlock_by_passcode_message_remote_wipe">Device locked. Wipe starting.</string>
    <string name="unlock_enter_passcode">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="unlock_button">Unlock</string>
    <string name="emergency_call">Emergency Call</string>
    <string name="end_call">End call</string>
    <string name="answer_call">Answer</string>
    <string name="forget_pwd_hint_text">If you do not remember the password, you can unlock your device at %s</string>
    <string name="lock_hint">Unlock</string>
    <string name="restore_system_locker_password">Your system lock password has been changed by Norton Mobile Security. Do you want to reset it?</string>
    <string name="input_lock_hint">Incorrect password, please try again.</string>
    <string name="btn_backup_contact">Backup</string>
    <string name="download_file_failed">Fail to download contact file.</string>
    <string name="backup_alert_normal_title">Backup Starting</string>
    <string name="name_bakcup_file">Name backup file:</string>
    <string name="restore_mode">Operation mode:</string>
    <string name="restore_alert_normal_title">Restore Starting</string>
    <string name="restore_from_device">Restore from:</string>
    <string name="backup_is_processing">Backup is processing</string>
    <string name="backup_is_finishing">Backup is finishing</string>
    <string name="restore_is_processing">Restore is processing</string>
    <string name="delete_timstamp_is_processing">Deleting backup</string>
    <string name="daily_backup">Daily backup</string>
    <string name="weekly_backup">Weekly backup</string>
    <string name="monthly_backup">Monthly backup</string>
    <string name="need_backup">Need Backup</string>
    <string name="backed_up">Current</string>
    <string name="no_contacts">No contacts</string>
    <string name="query_token_is_processing">Connecting…</string>
    <string name="contacts_in_cloud">Backed up contacts:</string>
    <string name="contacts_on_phone">Contacts on device:</string>
    <string name="of_string">of</string>
    <string name="gb_string">GB</string>
    <string name="loading_process">Loading…</string>
    <string name="last_backup_note">Last backup</string>
    <string name="error_status_title">Error</string>
    <string name="error_note_detail1">Could not connect to server</string>
    <string name="error_note_detail2">Not enough space on server for backup</string>
    <string name="warning_status_title">Note</string>
    <string name="warning_status_title1">Warning</string>
    <string name="warning_note_detail1">Battery is lower than 20%</string>
    <string name="warning_note_detail2">You are roaming</string>
    <string name="warning_note_detail3">The backup size is more than 20MB, Wifi is needed</string>
    <string name="warning_note_detail4">Your contact data has not changed since the last backup. Are you sure you want to run backup?</string>
    <string name="warning_note_detail5">Device does not have any contacts</string>
    <string name="top_error_note_1">No network connection</string>
    <string name="top_error_note_2">Service is not available</string>
    <string name="backup_period_label">Scheduled Backup: </string>
    <string name="backup_is_running">Backup is running</string>
    <string name="delete_is_running">Deletion is running</string>
    <string name="restore_is_running">Restore is running</string>
    <string name="delete_alert_normal_title">Are you sure you want to delete the selected backup files?</string>
    <string name="schedule_off">Off</string>
    <string name="schedule_daily">Daily</string>
    <string name="schedule_weekly">Weekly</string>
    <string name="schedule_monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="log_backup_module_name">Backup and Restore</string>
    <string name="log_backup_succ">Backup is successful.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_failed">Backup failed.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_deletion_succ">Delete backup successful.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_deletion_failed">Delete backup failed.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_deletion_patial_failed">Delete not completed. %d backup(s) deleted.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_pre_failed">Preparing server for account failed.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_restore_succ">Restore successful.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_restore_failed">Restore failed.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_battery">Scheduled backup is postponed to save power.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_activestate">Scheduled backup is postponed because device is active.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_token_environment">Scheduled backup is postponed because service is not initialized.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_restore">Scheduled backup is postponed because restore task is running.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_backup">Scheduled backup is postponed because backup task is running.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_network">Scheduled backup is postponed because WiFi is not connected.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_roaming_network">Scheduled backup is postponed because device is roaming.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_internet_unreachable">Scheduled backup is postponed because the Internet cannot be reached.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_connection_timeout">Scheduled backup is postponed because your connection has timed out.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_postponed_server_issue">Scheduled backup is postponed because there is an issue with the server.</string>
    <string name="log_backup_skip_no_change">No contacts updated, scheduled backup is skipped</string>
    <string name="log_backup_skip_expired">Your product has expired, backup failed.</string>
    <string name="backup_no_enough_space">Not enough space on server for backup. You can free space by deleting unneeded backups.</string>
    <string name="backup_tab_title">Backup</string>
    <string name="restore_tab_title">Restore</string>
    <string name="timestamp_sumary">"%1$s
%2$s contacts"</string>
    <string name="overwrite_mode">Overwrite</string>
    <string name="append_mode">Append</string>
    <string name="overwrite_mode_warnning">All local contacts will be rewritten.</string>
    <string name="use_default_backup_name">Use default name.</string>
    <string name="no_more_than_30_chars">Backup name should be no more than 30 chars.</string>
    <string name="no_special_chars">No special chars allowed.</string>
    <string name="invalid_input_backup_name">Invalid input.</string>
    <string name="resumable_restoration_txt">You have a resumable restoration task.</string>
    <string name="resume_restoration_txt">Resume</string>
    <string name="backup_failed">Backup Failed</string>
    <string name="restore_failed">Restore Failed</string>
    <string name="delete_timestamp_failed">Delete Backup file Failed</string>
    <string name="delete_timestamp_detail_result">Backup deletion failed: %1$s backup(s) deleted.</string>
    <string name="try_again">Please try again later</string>
    <string name="device_label">%1$s:</string>
    <string name="edit_label">Edit:</string>
    <string name="deleting_note">Deleting…</string>
    <string name="contacts_label">contacts</string>
    <string name="restore_top_info_text">To restore contacts to this device, first select a device and then a backup version to restore from.</string>
    <string name="select_device">select device</string>
    <string name="edit_text">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete_text">Delete</string>
    <string name="backup_to_list_view_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="toast_restoration_done">Restore successful.</string>
    <string name="toast_backup_done">Backup successful.</string>
    <string name="restore_version_mismatch">You need to upgrade Norton Mobile Security to the latest version to restore this backup.</string>
    <string name="restore_file_not_existed">Selected backup file does not exist any more on server.</string>
    <string name="backup_btn_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="backup_btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="selected_contacts">Selected Contacts:</string>
    <string name="zero">0</string>
    <string name="blocked_calls">Blocked Calls:</string>
    <string name="blocked_sms">Blocked SMS:</string>
    <string name="block_history">Block History</string>
    <string name="black_list">Block List</string>
    <string name="clean_history_alert">Are you sure you want to clean your Block History?</string>
    <string name="contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="call_log">Call Log</string>
    <string name="sms_log">SMS Log</string>
    <string name="input">Input</string>
    <string name="contact_search">Search</string>
    <string name="number">Number</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="add_from">Add from</string>
    <string name="call_time">Call time: </string>
    <string name="message_time">Message time: </string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number:</string>
    <string name="name_colon">Name:</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="block_calls">Block Calls</string>
    <string name="block_sms">Block SMS</string>
    <string name="add_to_black_dialog_message_multiple">The numbers will be added to your block list. Do you also want to remove them from your contacts list?</string>
    <string name="add_to_black_dialog_message_single">The number will be added to your block list. Do you also want to remove it from your contacts list?</string>
    <string name="add_to_black_dialog_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="add_to_black_dialog_no">No</string>
    <string name="number_already_in_block_list">The number is already in your block list.</string>
    <string name="choose_block_call_or_sms">Please choose block call or SMS.</string>
    <string name="empty_number_not_allowed">Empty number is not allowed.</string>
    <string name="wrong_number_not_allowed">Invalid phone number.</string>
    <string name="add_number">Add block number</string>
    <string name="block_unknown_tag">Unknown</string>
    <string name="block_list_empty">Your block list is empty.</string>
    <string name="tap_add_to_block">Tap \"+\" to enter the name and number of anyone whose calls or texts you want to block.</string>
    <string name="number_in_black_list">The incoming call %s is in block list.</string>
    <string name="need_setup">Not Set Up</string>
    <string name="feature_disabled">Off</string>
    <string name="scaning">Scanning…</string>
    <string name="app_conflict">App Conflict</string>
    <string name="network_error">Network Error</string>
    <string name="sms_only">SMS Lock Only</string>
    <string name="location_off">Location Off</string>
    <string name="setup_incomplete_toast">Norton Mobile Security setup incomplete.</string>
    <string name="open_anti_theft_web_portal">Open Web Portal…</string>
    <string name="log_passcode_wrong">Remote code is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_off_reply_wipe">Remote Wipe is currently off.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_enable">Remote wipe is off.</string>
    <string name="log_lock_enable">Remote Lock is off.</string>
    <string name="log_locate_enable">Remote locate is off</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_off_reply_locate">Remote Locate is currently off.</string>
    <string name="log_scream_enable">Remote scream is off</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_off_reply_scream">Remote Scream is currently off.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_contact">Deleting contacts.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_calllog">Deleting recent calls.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_sms">Deleting messages.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_browser">Deleting browser bookmark and history.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_sdcard">Wiping the SD card</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_sdcard_fail">Unable to wipe the SD card</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_no_sdcard">No SD card</string>
    <string name="log_unlock_blocked">Command blocked because sender is in block list.</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_off_reply_lock">Remote Lock is currently off.</string>
    <string name="device_already_locked">The target device is already locked.</string>
    <string name="log_sim_state_unknown">"Device locked because SIM card can't be detected."</string>
    <string name="log_sim_not_available_lock">Device locked because SIM card is missing.</string>
    <string name="log_sim_change_lock">Device locked because SIM card has been changed.</string>
    <string name="input_lock_hint_times">You have exceeded the number of login tries allowed. Security wipe is starting now.</string>
    <string name="input_lock_hint_with_security_wipe">Incorrect password! Please type it again. You have <b>%1$s</b> tries left.</string>
    <string name="input_lock_hint_with_security_wipe_1_only">Incorrect password! Please type it again. You have <b>1</b> try left.</string>
    <string name="unlock_by_passcode_message_remote_wipe_complete">Device locked. Wipe complete.</string>
    <string name="log_lock_triggered">Lock command triggered.</string>
    <string name="log_unlock_triggered">Unlock command triggered.</string>
    <string name="log_scream_triggered">Scream command triggered.</string>
    <string name="log_locate_triggered">Locate command triggered.</string>
    <string name="log_sneak_peek_triggered">Sneak peek command triggered.</string>
    <string name="log_wipe_triggered">Wipe command triggered.</string>
    <string name="wipe_ack_sucess">Remote wipe successful.</string>
    <string name="wipe_ack_fail">Remote wipe unsuccessful.</string>
    <string name="lock_ack_sucess">Remote lock successful.</string>
    <string name="lock_ack_fail">Remote lock unsuccessful.</string>
    <string name="locate_ack_fail">Remote locate unsuccessful.</string>
    <string name="locate_ack_fail_gps_off">Remote locate unsuccessful. GPS off.</string>
    <string name="scream_ack_sucess">Remote scream successful</string>
    <string name="scream_ack_fail">Remote scream unsuccessful</string>
    <string name="message_ack_sucess">Command successful.</string>
    <string name="message_ack_fail">Command unsuccessful.</string>
    <string name="migrating_title">Migration</string>
    <string name="migrating_info">Transferring data…</string>
    <string name="delete_interim_title">Data transferred</string>
    <string name="delete_interim_info">We have successfully transferred your license and personal data from previous version of Norton Mobile Security. You must uninstall that previous version to avoid system conflicts.</string>
    <string name="uninstall_old_nms_btn">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="quit_btn">Quit</string>
    <string name="delete_old_nms_title">Old version of NMS</string>
    <string name="delete_old_nms_info">We cannot upgrade your current version of Norton Mobile Security to the most recent version. Click Upgrade to upgrade your current version to an interim version, and then upgrade to the latest version.</string>
    <string name="launch_old_nms_btn">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="migration_warning_title">Data transfer error</string>
    <string name="retrieve_na_info">Retrieve Norton account…</string>
    <string name="retrieve_na_error_title">Failed to get license info</string>
    <string name="retrieve_na_error">Could not get your N360E license info, please retry later.</string>
    <string name="migration_error_info">Data transfer error while migrating data from the previous version of Norton Mobile Security. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="general_setting"><b>GENERAL SETTINGS</b></string>
    <string name="anti_theft_setting"><b>ANTI-THEFT</b></string>
    <string name="scans_setting"><b>SCANS</b></string>
    <string name="app_advisor_setting"><b>APP ADVISOR</b></string>
    <string name="live_update_setting"><b>LIVEUPDATE</b></string>
    <string name="live_update_last_update">Last Update:</string>
    <string name="live_update_manual_update">Run LiveUpdate</string>
    <string name="scan_for_gp">Scan for Google Play</string>
    <string name="scan_text_desc">Automatically scans apps before you install them</string>
    <string name="scan_setup_btn_text">Setup</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_title">LiveUpdate Running…</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_hide_window">Hide</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_stop_dowload">Cancel</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_without_wifi">The current network is not WiFi. Are you sure you want to run LiveUpdate?</string>
    <string name="liveudpate_running">Scheduled LiveUpdate is currently running. Try again later.</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_initialize">Initializing LiveUpdate…</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_download_catalog">Downloading catalog file…</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_process_update">Processing update list</string>
    <string name="liveupdate_download_update">Downloading updates…</string>
    <string name="help_anti_malware_title">Anti-Malware</string>
    <string name="help_anti_malware">Anti-Malware protects you from mobile threats by scanning for and removing malicious apps.</string>
    <string name="help_grayware_title">App Advisor</string>
    <string name="help_app_advisor_content_1">Get warnings about apps installed on your device with issues like personal information leaks, ads, data transfer and excessive battery consumption.</string>
    <string name="help_app_advisor_content_2">Just enable App Advisor for Google Play in Settings to see this information before you download an app.</string>
    <string name="help_call_blocking_title">Call &amp; SMS Blocking</string>
    <string name="help_call_blocking">Call &amp; SMS Blocking helps guard your privacy from unwanted calls and texts.</string>
    <string name="help_liveupdate_title">LiveUpdate</string>
    <string name="help_liveupdate">LiveUpdate keeps your mobile protection current by automatically checking for new threat definitions and new Norton components.</string>
    <string name="help_lockwipe_title">Anti-Theft</string>
    <string name="help_lockwipe">"If your device is lost or stolen, you have several options for recovering it using text commands or commands from the Norton Mobile Security Website. 

Using texts, you can lock, wipe, and locate your device and you can cause it to make noise. The text message should consist of an action word (lock, wipe, locate, or scream) followed by your passcode."</string>
    <string name="help_admin_lockwipe">"If your device is lost or stolen, your device administrator can do the following: 

 - Remotely lock, wipe, and locate your device
 - Cause the device to make a noise
 - Trigger the device's camera to take a picture of whatever is in front of it"</string>
    <string name="help_web_lockwipe">On the website, you can also lock and locate your device. In addition, you can trigger your device’s camera to take a picture of whoever or whatever is in front of it to help you retrieve it.</string>
    <string name="help_lockwipe_settings">Additional Anti-Theft options are available in Settings.</string>
    <string name="help_web_protection_title">Web Protection</string>
    <string name="help_web_protection">Web Protection detects and warns you about fraudulent websites before you visit them.</string>
    <string name="help_support_title">Support</string>
    <string name="help_support">Click here for support</string>
    <string name="product_support_link">http://norton.com/nms_support</string>
    <string name="help_device_admin_intro">"We recommend that you turn on Security Lock for Norton Mobile Security to keep your device protected in case it is started in Safe Mode.
 To turn on Security Lock:

 1. On the Norton Mobile Security main screen, tap Menu.
 2. On the Menu screen, tap Settings.
 3. On the Settings screen, tap Security Lock.

 Please note that Security Lock will need to be turned off in order to uninstall Norton Mobile Security."</string>
    <string name="help_battery_saving_title">Battery Saving Mode</string>
    <string name="help_battery_saving_intro">Postpones scheduled LiveUpdate or scans when the battery is low until the battery is charged.</string>
    <string name="help_backup_title">Backup</string>
    <string name="help_backup_content">"Securely back up the contacts on your device online and restore them to this device or any other device that also has Norton Mobile Security installed.
When you restore a backup, you have two choices: Append or Overwrite. Append adds the contacts you don't already have on your device. Overwrite replaces your current contact list with the backed up list."</string>
    <string name="help_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="help_policy">Please go to:</string>
    <string name="product_policy_link">http://www.norton.mobi/privacy-policy</string>
    <string name="about_version_title">Version:</string>
    <string name="about_version_V">V</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">Open Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="main_copyright">Copyright© 1991–2015 Symantec Corporation.</string>
    <string name="main_allright">All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="no_app_share">No application handling share action is found.</string>
    <string name="share_subject">Protect your mobile device!</string>
    <string name="share_text">"Hi. I'm using Norton Mobile Security to protect my mobile device from malware and theft. It has features like anti-malware, App Advisor, Web protection, call and SMS blocking (for phones), backup and restore of contacts, and anti-theft. So you can protect your device and the important stuff on it, try it here: "</string>
    <string name="share_china_text">http://norton.mobi/cn/nms-multi-platform-download</string>
    <string name="share_general_text">http://bit.ly/sharenms</string>
    <string name="log_malware_update_key">Public key exists, no need to update.</string>
    <string name="log_malware_set_key">Public key is set by command.</string>
    <string name="log_locate">Remote Locate</string>
    <string name="log_anti_theft">Anti-Theft</string>
    <string name="locate_message">Device location (within %1$d meters):%2$s,%3$s</string>
    <string name="locate_uri">http://maps.google.com/maps?q=%1$s,%2$s</string>
    <string name="gps_off_toast">Remote Locate is off because GPS is off.</string>
    <string name="user_rate_tip">Now that you have had a chance to use Norton Mobile Security, would you like to rate it on Google Play?</string>
    <string name="rate_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="rate_no">No</string>
    <string name="rate_later">Later</string>
    <string name="install_error_dialog_title">Norton Mobile Security Error</string>
    <string name="install_error_dialog_text">Norton Mobile Security cannot protect this device from the SD card. Please install the product on the device’s internal memory.</string>
    <string name="google_play_norton_apps">https://play.google.com/store/apps/developer?id=NortonMobile</string>
    <string name="purchase">Purchase</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="register_info">Your purchase from Google was successful, but is not yet registered with Symantec. Please click Register to complete your upgrade.</string>
    <string name="sign_and_upgrade">Sign in and Upgrade</string>
    <string name="upgrade_title">Upgrade to full version to add:</string>
    <string name="upgrade_title_sos">Sign in to access the following features:</string>
    <string name="upgrade_title_sos_after_signin">Activate to access the following features:</string>
    <string name="sync_license_title">Synchronize license to get the following features back:</string>
    <string name="upgrade_sms_at">SMS Scream, Wipe, and Locate</string>
    <string name="upgrade_sms_at_jp">SMS Lock, Scream, Wipe, and Locate</string>
    <string name="upgrade_web_at">Web Lock, Scream, Wipe, Locate, and Sneak Peek</string>
    <string name="upgrade_call_blocking">Call and SMS Blocking</string>
    <string name="upgrade_web_protection">Web Protection</string>
    <string name="upgrade_app_advisor">App Advisor</string>
    <string name="upgrade_anti_malware">Anti-Malware</string>
    <string name="upgrade_devices">Registration for multiple devices</string>
    <string name="update_license">Updating license…</string>
    <string name="have_key">I have already purchased the product</string>
    <string name="iab_ongoing">Google in-app billing is running, please wait.</string>
    <string name="purchase_failed">Purchase could not be completed. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="register_error">Unable to register your purchase right now. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="skip_trial_and_purchase">Skip trial and purchase premium today</string>
    <string name="license_info">License Information</string>
    <string name="license_account">Signed in as:</string>
    <string name="license_type">Product Info:</string>
    <string name="psn">Serial Number:</string>
    <string name="autorenew">Auto Renew:</string>
    <string name="license_remain_days">Subscription:</string>
    <string name="remaindays">%1$d days left</string>
    <string name="visit_portal_desc">For more details, visit</string>
    <string name="norton_one_renew_message">Learn more about how to get a Norton One membership at &lt;b>one.norton.com&lt;/b>.</string>
    <string name="neos_renew_message">Your copy of Norton Mobile Security is part of a multi-platform offering. Go to &lt;b>manage.norton.com&lt;/b> to renew your subscription.</string>
    <string name="nortonone_url">https://one.norton.com/</string>
    <string name="management_url">https://manage.norton.com/</string>
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="inactive">Inactive</string>
    <string name="license_sync_fail">License server connection error. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="license_sync_running">Another license synchronization task is already running.</string>
    <string name="not_signin">Not signed in</string>
    <string name="nms">Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="at_conflict">App Conflict</string>
    <string name="conflict_full">You must uninstall Norton Anti-Theft in order to avoid any application conflicts with Norton Mobile Security. Click Uninstall below to remove Norton Anti-Theft.</string>
    <string name="uninstall_at">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="conflict_lite_title">Norton Anti-Theft</string>
    <string name="conflict_lite">"Because Norton Anti-Theft is already installed on this device, the Anti-Theft feature of Norton Mobile Security Lite will be turned off. 
 We recommend that you upgrade to the full version of Norton Mobile Security for more comprehensive Anti-Theft protection."</string>
    <string name="launch_at">Start Norton Anti-Theft</string>
    <string name="upgrade">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="btn_retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="auto_login_failed">Auto login failed. Please enter your Norton account and Password manually.</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_title">For SMS Commands</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_passcode_show">Your Passcode is</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_function_show">With this passcode, you can use SMS commands to:</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_lock_or_not">Lock your device</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_locate">Locate your device</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_remote">Scream your device</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_wipe">Wipe your data from your device</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_service_link">Find out more or change your passcode at %s</string>
    <string name="anti_theft_dialog_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="ncw">Norton Community Watch</string>
    <string name="force_lu_start_btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="force_lu_start_btn_start">Update</string>
    <string name="force_lu_title_valid">Stay Protected</string>
    <string name="force_lu_title_invalid">Norton Mobile Security is switched off</string>
    <string name="force_lu_notification_title">Update Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="force_lu_notification_message">Get the latest version and stay protected.</string>
    <string name="force_lu_message_valid">Get the latest version of Norton Mobile Security.</string>
    <string name="force_lu_message_invalid">Get the latest version of the app and stay protected.</string>
    <string name="greyware_trust_btn">Trust Anyway</string>
    <string name="greyware_uninstall_btn">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="subscription_days">Subscription Days: %1$d</string>
    <string name="resident_notification_text_license_remaining_renew">Renew to stay protected</string>
    <string name="convert_to_freemium_renew">Renew to extend protection</string>
    <string name="samsung_apps_not_found">Samsung Apps is not found!</string>
    <string name="blocked_prompt">Malicious Website Blocked</string>
    <string name="exit_text">Exit this site</string>
    <string name="detail_text"><u>View Details</u></string>
    <string name="continue_site_text"><u>Continue to site</u></string>
    <string name="continue_text">Continue</string>
    <string name="wp_ok_text">OK</string>
    <string name="continue_html">Continue Anyway</string>
    <string name="blocked_reason_1">This is a known malicious website. It is recommended that you do NOT visit this site.</string>
    <string name="blocked_reason_2">This site is a known malicious website. We recommend that you close the tab without visiting the site.</string>
    <string name="prompt_title">JavaScript Disabled</string>
    <string name="javascript_prompt">For better protection of your browser, JavaScript must be enabled.</string>
    <string name="javascript_prompt_title">JavaScript Disabled</string>
    <string name="javascript_prompt_content">Please enable JavaScript otherwise we can not protect you.</string>
    <string name="wp_app_name">Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="sdcard_prompt">For better protection of your browser:</string>
    <string name="sdcard_prompt1">Insert your SD Card</string>
    <string name="sdcard_prompt2">DO NOT go back to previous web page.</string>
    <string name="loading_cc">Loading…</string>
    <string name="exiting_cc">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="form_resubmit">To display this page, we must send information that will repeat any action (such as a search or order confirmation) that was performed earlier. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="ssl_error">Please make sure your device time is correct. Otherwise, you have attempted to reach a site whose security certificate is not trusted by the operating system on your device!</string>
    <string name="http_error">A problem occurred while trying to communicate with the server. Please check your network settings. Do you want to retry now?</string>
    <string name="switch_accout_error">Incorrect account. Please use the account associated with this product.</string>
    <string name="login_generic_error">Failed to login.</string>
    <string name="activate_error">Activate</string>
    <string name="activate_now">Activate Now</string>
    <string name="notification_provisional">Sign in to Activate</string>
    <string name="trial_layout_title">30-Day Premium Trial</string>
    <string name="trial_upgrade_title">Premium version adds:</string>
    <string name="upgrade_jp_version">Upgrade adds:</string>
    <string name="trial_feature_app_advisor">Warns about bad apps</string>
    <string name="trial_feature_backup">Saves your contact list</string>
    <string name="trial_feature_callblocking">Blocks unwanted calls and texts</string>
    <string name="trial_feature_webprotection">Warns about bad websites</string>
    <string name="trial_layout_decription">One trial per Norton Account</string>
    <string name="activate_button">Start Trial</string>
    <string name="seat_disabled">Norton Mobile Security has been disabled on this device by the user.</string>
    <string name="key_refunded">The activation key has been refunded.</string>
    <string name="activation_fail">License activation failed. Error code:</string>
    <string name="server_unavailable">Cannot connect to the server. Please check your network settings or try again later.</string>
    <string name="create_entitlement_failed">Create entitlement failed.</string>
    <string name="device_datetime_invalid">Device date/time does not match with server.</string>
    <string name="register_product_failed">Product Registration failed.</string>
    <string name="billing_user_canceled">User cancelled.</string>
    <string name="billing_item_unavailable">Purchased item not exist.</string>
    <string name="billing_unavailable">You either have not set up a Google account or Google in-app billing is not available in your country.</string>
    <string name="billing_developer_error">Purchase cannot be completed due to a program error.</string>
    <string name="billing_service_unavailable">The billing service is unavailable. Please check your network connection, make sure it is correct.</string>
    <string name="billing_communicate_error">Unable to communicate with Google Play Store service. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="billing_market_not_install_error">Error! Google Play is not found!</string>
    <string name="billing_donut_market_version_error">You need to update your version of Android Market to 2.3.4 (or higher).</string>
    <string name="billing_honeycomb_market_version_error">You need to update your version of Android Market to 5.0.12 (or higher).</string>
    <string name="billing_android_version_error">Your version of Android does not support in-app purchases. Please update your Android operating system to a newer version.</string>
    <string name="billing_bind_market_service_error">Unable to establish communication with Google Play Store service. Please restart your device and try again.</string>
    <string name="billing_background_data_error">Please enable \"Background data\" sync in \"Settings\" -> \"Accounts and sync\" before purchase.</string>
    <string name="billing_error">An unexpected Google server error. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="billing_unknown_error">An unexpected error has occurred. Please restart your device and try again.</string>
    <string name="symantec_server_error">An unexpected Symantec server error. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="internal_error">An internal error has occurred. Please restart your device and try again.</string>
    <string name="korea_warning_text">This device is equipped with Norton Mobile Security. If you continue to use this device, you consent that it will collect your location and/or images of you and send them to Symantec Corporation in the US where they will be retained until the owner requests deletion. Up to 10 images/locations will be retained and provided to the owner, who registered with Symantec for the purposes of tracking this device.</string>
    <string name="notify_title">Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="notify_safe">Your device is protected</string>
    <string name="notify_risk_malware_only">Malware found</string>
    <string name="notify_scanning">Scanning …</string>
    <string name="notify_malicious">%1$s is malicious</string>
    <string name="notify_risky">App alert: %1$s</string>
    <string name="notify_clean">%1$s is safe</string>
    <string name="notify_action_uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="notify_action_trust">Trust</string>
    <string name="notify_action_view">View</string>
    <string name="notify_action_renew">Renew</string>
    <string name="notify_title_eula_changed">Accept EULA</string>
    <string name="notify_promote_eula_changed">Please accept the updated EULA and Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="notify_title_trial">Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="notify_promote_trial">Get Premium FREE for %1$d days</string>
    <string name="notify_free_trial">Start Free Premium Trial</string>
    <string name="notify_promote_trial_big">Get added protection for your device with Norton Mobile Security Premium FREE for %1$d days.</string>
    <string name="notify_will_expire">Norton Mobile expires in %1$d days</string>
    <string name="notify_will_lost">You will be losing a lot of valuable features</string>
    <string name="notify_will_lost_big">"You will be missing these features:
"</string>
    <string name="notify_lost_features">"• App Advisor - warns about bad apps
• Contacts backup - you can access your contacts anywhere
• Web Protection - safe browsing ensures your privacy is protected
• Call Blocking - blocks unwanted calls and texts."</string>
    <string name="notify_lost_big">"You missed these features:
"</string>
    <string name="notify_title_manual_backup">Backup reminder</string>
    <string name="notify_manual_backup_remainder">You have not run backup for 7 days.</string>
    <string name="notify_title_schedule_backup">Missing backup</string>
    <string name="notify_schedule_backup_remainder">Tap to run a backup…</string>
    <string name="advisor_tips">These apps have issues you should review. Tap an app for more info.</string>
    <string name="advisor_no_risk">No problem apps found.</string>
    <string name="advisor_apps">Apps</string>
    <string name="advisor_highest_concern">High Risk</string>
    <string name="advisor_low_medium_concern">Medium Risk</string>
    <string name="advisor_trusted">Trusted Apps</string>
    <string name="advisor_tips_trusted">These apps you have trusted even though they have issues.</string>
    <string name="advisor_trust_successed">This app is trusted</string>
    <string name="advisor_trust_failed">Cannot trust this app</string>
    <string name="trial_ends_title">Your Premium Trial Has Ended</string>
    <string name="trial_ends_jp_title">Your Trial Has Ended</string>
    <string name="trial_hint_info">The following features are no longer available:</string>
    <string name="trial_back_msg">Get Premium</string>
    <string name="btn_upgrade">Get Premium</string>
    <string name="btn_upgrade_trial">Start Trial</string>
    <string name="premium_renew">Renew now to continue using:</string>
    <string name="renew_now">Renew Now</string>
    <string name="premium_mark">Premium</string>
    <string name="malware_scanning">Scan in progress</string>
    <string name="malware_found_warnings_desc">Malware is dangerous and should be removed.</string>
    <string name="malware_found_warnings">We found malware</string>
    <string name="malware_scan_complete">Malware Scan Complete</string>
    <string name="malware_not_exist_page_title">No malware found</string>
    <string name="malware_go_advisor_button">App Advisor</string>
    <string name="malware_start_trial_button">Start FREE Premium Trial</string>
    <string name="malware_go_premium_button">Get Premium</string>
    <string name="malware_scan_no_risk_message">Malware scan now runs automatically so your device is always protected.</string>
    <string name="malware_go_advisor_no_risk_content">App Advisor can tell you about apps containing other risks, such as information leaks.</string>
    <string name="malware_start_trial_content">Get more info about your apps with our new premium App Advisor. Try all the premium features &lt;b>FREE for %d days.&lt;/b></string>
    <string name="malware_go_premium_content">Did you know? App Advisor in Norton Mobile Security Premium can tell you about apps containing other risks, such as information leaks.</string>
    <string name="malware_remove_file_title">Malware File</string>
    <string name="malware_remove_file_message">"Do you want to remove this malware file on storage?

 %s?"</string>
    <string name="scan_in_processing">Scan is in process.</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome to Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">"Norton Mobile Security detects malware and our new App Advisor tells you if any apps are collecting private information, contain adware, or are draining your battery or sending data when you're not using the app.

Now users can try out all the features "<b>FREE for 30 days</b> just by creating an account. After that, you can upgrade to a premium account or keep Norton Mobile Security Lite with Malware Scan.</string>
    <string name="welcome_next">Next</string>
    <string name="whats_new_title">"What's New"</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text"><b>New in this version of Norton Mobile Security:</b></string>
    <string name="whats_new_text1">An App Advisor feature that detects:</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text1_bullet">-</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text1_part1">Adware</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text1_part2">Collection or sharing of personal data</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text1_part3">Background network usage</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text1_part4">Background battery usage</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text2">Scan is now accessible from the menu list.</string>
    <string name="whats_new_text3">Scheduled Scan and LiveUpdate is now accessible from the Settings menu.</string>
    <string name="bullet">•</string>
    <string name="whats_new_next">Next</string>
    <string name="whats_new_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="app_advisor">App Advisor by Norton</string>
    <string name="helpful_feedback">Was this info helpful?</string>
    <string name="network_unavailable">Network Unavailable</string>
    <string name="check_network">Check your Internet connection and try again later.</string>
    <string name="server_cannot_connect">Cannot connect to the server. Try again later.</string>
    <string name="no_info_available">No info available</string>
    <string name="no_info_yet">"We don't have any info about this app yet. Check back soon."</string>
    <string name="invalid_content">Link Missing</string>
    <string name="invalid_content_text">The shared data does not contain a link to an app.</string>
    <string name="not_supported">Unsupported Shared Data</string>
    <string name="not_supported_text">Only shared data from Google Play App is currently supported.</string>
    <string name="feature_unavailable">Feature not yet enabled</string>
    <string name="feature_unavailable_text">Please ensure you have properly activated Norton Mobile Security before using.</string>
    <string name="invalid_google_play">Update Your Google Play</string>
    <string name="invalid_google_play_text">To see App Advisor information on apps before you download them, you need to install the latest version of Google Play.</string>
    <string name="app_published">Published %s than three weeks ago</string>
    <string name="less">less</string>
    <string name="more">more</string>
    <string name="malware_warning">This app contains malware.</string>
    <string name="malware_dont_download">Installing is not recommended.</string>
    <string name="personal_data">Personal Data Shared</string>
    <string name="personal_data_safe">Your data is safe</string>
    <string name="PHONE_NUMBER">Device phone number</string>
    <string name="SIM_CARD_INFO">SIM card details</string>
    <string name="ACCOUNT_INFO">Personal account details</string>
    <string name="AUDIO_INFO">Recorded audio clips</string>
    <string name="CALENDAR_INFO">Calendar event details</string>
    <string name="CALL_LOG">Call log details</string>
    <string name="CAMERA_INFO">Pictures</string>
    <string name="CONTACT_INFO">Contact details</string>
    <string name="SMS_INFO">SMS messages</string>
    <string name="LOCATION_INFO">Location</string>
    <string name="OPERATOR_INFO">Network operator details</string>
    <string name="DEVICE_INFO">Device details</string>
    <string name="INSTALLED_APP_INFO">Installed app details</string>
    <string name="RUNNING_APP_INFO">Running app details</string>
    <string name="BROWSER_HISTORY">Browser history</string>
    <string name="BROWSER_BOOKMARKS">Browser bookmarks</string>
    <string name="SETTINGS_INFO">Settings info</string>
    <string name="PHONE_NUMBER_LONG">Collects and sends phone number. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="SIM_CARD_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends SIM card details, including address book, mobile PIN, and call history. This can add charges to data plan and is a MED privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="ACCOUNT_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends personal account details, including account user names and passwords. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="AUDIO_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends recorded audio clips. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="CALENDAR_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends calendar event details. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="CALL_LOG_LONG">Collects and sends call log details, including date, duration, and phone numbers. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="CAMERA_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends pictures. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="CONTACT_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends address book details. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="SMS_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends SMS messages. This can add charges to data plan and is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="LOCATION_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends your location info. This can add charges to data plan and is a LOW privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="OPERATOR_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends mobile network details, including operator name, country, and MNC/MCC. This can add charges to data plan and is a LOW privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="DEVICE_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends device info, including brand, model, OS, IMEI number. This can add charges to data plan and is a LOW privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="INSTALLED_APP_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends list of installed apps and app details. This can add charges to data plan and is a LOW privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="RUNNING_APP_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends list of apps running at a specific time. This can add charges to data plan and is a MED privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="BROWSER_HISTORY_LONG">Collects and sends browser history. This can add charges to data plan and is a MED privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="BROWSER_BOOKMARKS_LONG">Collects and sends browser bookmarks. This can add charges to data plan and is a MED privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="SETTINGS_INFO_LONG">Collects and sends device settings info, including ringer, Bluetooth, and sleep settings. This can add charges to data plan and is a LOW privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="ads_displayed">Ads Displayed</string>
    <string name="no_app_ads">No Ads</string>
    <string name="no_app_ads_long">No ad networks found in this app, but may contain ads embedded in content.</string>
    <string name="inside_app_ads">In-App</string>
    <string name="outside_app_ads">Intrusive</string>
    <string name="NOTIFICATION_BAR_ADS">Puts ads on notification bar. </string>
    <string name="SHORTCUT_ADS">Adds icons to home screen. </string>
    <string name="BOOKMARK_ADS">Modifies browser bookmarks. </string>
    <string name="DIALTONE_ADS">Plays audio ads after dialing. </string>
    <string name="SMS_INBOX_ADS">Displays ads in SMS inbox. </string>
    <string name="CLICK_SMS">Sends an SMS when clicking ads. </string>
    <string name="IN_CONTEXT_ADS">Displays ads while in use, including banners, pop-ups, and other graphics. These ads are common in free apps. </string>
    <string name="low">Low</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="battery_drain">Background Battery Usage</string>
    <string name="battery_drain_none">Only uses battery when app is in use.</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_usage">Background Data Usage</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_usage_none">Only uses mobile data when app is in use.</string>
    <string name="unusual_behavior">Unusual Behaviors Detected</string>
    <string name="no_unusual_behaviors">No unusual behaviors found</string>
    <string name="INSTALL_APP">Prompts to install other apps.</string>
    <string name="SELF_UPDATE">Automatically updates itself with new features.</string>
    <string name="CHANGE_HOMEPAGE">Changes your browser home screen.</string>
    <string name="INSTALL_APP_LONG">Prompts you to install other apps. Apps cannot be installed without your permission, but prompt can be intrusive. This is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="SELF_UPDATE_LONG">Automatically updates itself with new features without your permission. Updates may not be malicious and could be part of normal app function. This is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="CHANGE_HOMEPAGE_LONG">Changes your browser home screen. This is a HIGH privacy risk.</string>
    <string name="unknown_data">No data available</string>
    <string name="user_feedback_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="user_feedback_no">No</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">App Advisor by Norton</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">"App Advisor automatically scans apps in Google Play before you install them, looking for risky or annoying behavior. Web Protection protects you from entering fraudulent websites. 

Both features require your permission to observe your actions and retrieve app content and website addresses, all of which is used for the sole purpose of feature functionality. This information is never stored or shared. 

Turn on this setting to allow App Advisor and Web Protection to function."</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_setup_toast">Find and tap on App Advisor by Norton</string>
    <string name="accessibility_settings_not_found">Sorry, we did not find Accessibility Settings on your device.</string>
    <string name="step_number_1">1.</string>
    <string name="step_number_2">2.</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_setup_subheader">Tap to set up</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_setup">Set Up</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_intro_1">App Advisor automatically scans Google Play apps before you install them.</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_intro_2">To set up this feature:</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_tutorial_step_1">Tap <b>Set Up</b>" and find
"<b>App Advisor by Norton</b>.</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_tutorial_step_2">Turn <b>ON</b> App Advisor.</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_tutorial_subtext">You can set up later in Settings</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_setup_success">Setup Success</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_google_play_instruction">"Open Google Play and tap any app.

App Advisor will automatically scan that app and display the results."</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_google_play_toast">Tap any app. App Advisor will automatically scan that app and display the results.</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_try_in_google_play">Try in Google Play</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_no_google_play_error">Have you installed Google Play Store?</string>
    <string name="app_store_analyzer_general_error">Something went wrong, try again</string>
    <string name="notify_title_app_advisor_for_google_play">App Advisor for Google Play</string>
    <string name="notify_text_app_store_analyzer_pending_google_play">Set up now for proactive protection.</string>
    <string name="notify_title_app_store_analyzer_for_upgrade_user">New in Norton Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="notify_text_app_store_analyzer_for_upgrade_user">App Advisor for Google Play</string>
    <string name="notify_title_app_store_analyzer_blacklisted">Disable App Advisor for Google Play</string>
    <string name="notify_text_app_store_analyzer_blacklisted">Your device has issues running App Advisor for Google Play. To help maintain performance, tap <b>Disable</b> to open the Accessibility page, find App Advisor by Norton, and turn it OFF.</string>
    <string name="auto_scan_high_concern">High Risk</string>
    <string name="auto_scan_medium_concern">Medium Risk</string>
    <string name="auto_scan_no_concern">No Risk</string>
    <string name="auto_scan_no_info">No Info</string>
    <string name="auto_scan_error">Error</string>
    <string name="auto_scan_server_error">Server Unavailable</string>
    <string name="intro_free_trial_title">FREE 30-Day Premium Trial</string>
    <string name="intro_header_text">Mobile Security</string>
    <string name="intro_page_next">Next</string>
    <string name="intro_free_trial_content">"Sign up for a Norton account and try all Premium features FREE for 30 days, including:
\u0009\u0009• App Advisor
\u0009\u0009• Backup
\u0009\u0009• Web Protection
\u0009\u0009• Call and SMS blocking
Then upgrade to a Premium account or keep using the free Norton Mobile Security including Anti-Malware scan."</string>
    <string name="intro_app_advisor_content">App Advisor automatically scans the app and shows the results.</string>
    <string name="intro_app_advisor_footer">(setup required)</string>
    <string name="intro_app_advisor_subtilte">Open Google Play and tap any app.</string>
    <string name="intro_app_advisor_title">App Advisor for Google Play</string>
    <string name="admin_dialog_title">Get Better Protection</string>
    <string name="admin_dialog_button_text">Activate</string>
    <string name="admin_dialog_active_later_text">You can activate later in Settings.</string>
    <string name="log_management_module_name">Management</string>
    <string name="log_management_admin_lock_setting">Admin locked the <b>%1$s</b>" setting. "</string>
    <string name="log_management_admin_unlock_setting">Admin unlocked the <b>%1$s</b>" setting. "</string>
    <string name="log_management_setting_scan_schedule">Scan Schedule</string>
    <string name="log_management_setting_webprotection">Web Protection</string>
    <string name="log_management_setting_scan_sd_card">Scan SD Card</string>
    <string name="log_managment_change_setting">Admin set the <b>%1$s</b> as <b>%2$s</b>.</string>
    <string name="log_management_liveupdate_initiated">Admin initiated LiveUpdate.</string>
    <string name="log_management_scan_initiated">Admin initiated anti-malware scan.</string>
    <string name="debug_launch_remote_command">Remote Command</string>
</resources>
